Now that the hyperparameter tuning job has finished up,
超参数优化作业运行完毕后
we can test our model to see how well it's doing.
我们可以测试模型 看看运行效果
As before, first of what we do is we create
和之前一样 首先新建一个 estimator 对象
a new estimator object by attaching it to a training job which has already completed.
然后将其连接到已经完成的训练作业上
In this case, we want to attach it to the best training job that
我们将其附加到在超参数优化作业中
was found during the hyperparameter tuning job.
发现的最佳训练作业
Now, we have a trained estimator and we can
我们已经有了训练过的 estimator
use that trained estimator to create a transformer object.
可以使用训练的 estimator 创建 transformer 对象
Once we've done that, we can start our batch transform job to test our model.
然后开始批转换作业以测试模型
As before, remember that the transform job is done in the background
和之前一样 转换作业在后台运行
so we need to call the weight method to wait for the transform job to finish up.
需要调用 wait() 方法等待转换作业运行完毕
It seems that the batch transform job failed.
批转换作业似乎失败了
So, why might this be?
为何？
Well, unfortunately, the output here doesn't
遗憾的是 这里的输出结果
quite seem to lead us to what the issue might be.
并没有清晰地告诉我们问题在哪
In fact, down here at the bottom it says,
实际上 在底部有条消息
"See job logs for more information."
“See job logs for more information.”
So, this seems like a good opportunity to take a look at CloudWatch to see
看来需要打开 CloudWatch
what output this batch transform job
检查下该批转换作业的输出是什么
generated and to see if we can figure out what the error might be.
并看看错误在哪
If we go back to the SageMaker console and look down here under batch transform jobs,
切换到 SageMaker 控制台 点击列表底部的“Batch transform jobs”
we can see that batch transform job that failed.
可以在右侧看到失败的批转换作业
Selecting this transform job and scrolling down to the monitor section,
选择这个转换作业 向下滚动到“Monitor”部分
we want to click on the view logs link which will
点击“View logs”链接
open up the CloudWatch logs for this batch transform job.
打开此批转换作业的 CloudWatch 日志
We want to take a look at the data log here.
我们看看 data-log
If I do that and click on it and I look at the listing here it says that for some reason,
点击打开该日志 看到有个列表项提到
when reading the test dataset, there is an issue.
在读取测试数据集时 出错了
If I look even closer and I start expanding each of these errors,
展开每项错误
we can see right here that this error tells us that
这个错误提示
the inference data that was sent had 5,001 columns,
发送的推理数据有 5,001 列
whereas the number of features that should be presented at inference time is only 5,000.
而在推理时应该出现的特征数量只有 5,000 个
What this seems to imply is that there's
这表明我们创建测试数据集时
some issue in the way that we've created our test dataset.
出现了某种问题
So, if we go back to the notebook and scroll all the way
回到 notebook
back up to where we created the test dataset,
一直滚动到测试数据集的创建部分
we can try and inspect and see where the issue might arise.
看看问题可能出在哪
Now, it appears as though we saved
看起来我们按照保存验证集和训练集的方式
the test dataset in the same way that we save the validation and training datasets.
保存了测试集
Remember though that the training and validation
训练和验证集
datasets require the ground truth labels,
需要真实标签
but the test dataset does not.
但是测试集不需要
So, this is the wrong way to go about saving the test dataset.
所以保存测试集的方式错了
So, it should have had here is this line right here.
应该使用这行代码
That is we just save the test dataset
即将测试集直接保存到 csv 中
directly to csv and we do not include the ground truth labels.
不包含真实标签
Once we've done that,
完成这一步后
we need to make sure to upload the new test dataset to S3.
我们需要将新的测试集上传到 S3
Once that's done, we can run the batch transform job again making sure to
然后重新运行批转换作业
include the location of
指定新上传的
the newly uploaded correct test dataset and then wait for it to finish.
正确测试集所在的位置 然后等待运行完毕
Now, the batch transform job has finished up,
批转换作业运行完毕后
we can copy the output files to
我们将输出文件复制到
the local notebook instance and check to see how well our model is doing.
本地 notebook 记事本 看看模型的表现如何